

- Erzurum, Yakutiye
- □ 05529379981
- ✓ sedanurakdg@gmail.com

SKILLS

- . Python Flask
- Git
- Java Spring Boot
- HTML.CSS.Javascript
- Angular
- Typescript
- iQuery
- NET Core
- PostgreSQL
- Wordpress
- Figma
- Linux
- H2DB
- JDBCWeb Services (REST)
- Microservices
- OO Design patterns
- JPA, Hibernate
- Flexible worker
- Multitasking

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- JavaScript programming
- · Programming Java Spring Boot
- API design knowledge
- Code reviews
- Algorithm implementation
- Product development
- Clean Code

LANGUAGES

Turkish: First Language

English:

B2

Upper Intermediate

Sedanur Akdağ

SUMMARY

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering. Software development professional with experience in developing and designing web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular. Adept at developing and deploying complex backend systems using JAVA□Spring Boot, web services and databases.

EXPERIENCE

July 2022 - Current

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Saat Teknoloji | Kastamonu, Merkez

- Reviewed code, debugged problems, and corrected issues.
- Designed and developed forward-thinking systems that meet user needs and improve productivity.
- Provided software application engineering and maintenance for development lifecycle.
- Worked with back-end developers to design APIs. In the field of OTT in the company I work for. I use Angular for the UI.
- · Coded backend services using Spring Boot.
- Wrote and defined clean codes to achieve functional and sustainable web applications.
- Operated within Agile methodology for efficient project progress.

September 2019 - November 2019

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN İnnova Bilişim Çözümleri | Ankara, Çankaya

- Developed REST project using Java-Spring Boot and Python□Flask programming language.
- Supported development, QA and user experience staff to develop new products.
- Worked with developers to identify and remove software bugs.
- Attended training to learn software development theory, techniques and coding best practices.

June 2016 - July 2016

NETWORK ENGÎNEER INTERN Înnova Bilişim Çözümleri | Ankara, Çankaya

- Provided network support and performed troubleshooting to resolve various WAN/LAN connectivity issues.
- Installed and maintained data and voice circuits through routers, switches and WAN devices.
- Demonstrated strong analytical, troubleshooting and problem ☐solving skills.
- Advanced knowledge of large-scale global enterprise network operations and security.
- Took CCNA trainings and created many network topologies. I practiced on Cisco devices
- Maintained hardware and software for networks and assisted in installation and upgrade of servers.

EDUCATION

2020 Computer Engineering Ataturk University, Erzurum, 25